Makishima has been arrested.
The helmet criminals have been wiped out.
The case is closed. Is it all over now?
Kagari is missing.
There was an Enforcer from Division 2 who managed to escape during all the confusion.
Inspector... Do you think Kagari would run off?
I would like to show
槙島は逮捕
Cut open my skull
Look into my head
ヘルメット犯罪者たちは壊滅
I don't know why I'm so harsh
一件落着…
I could be so brash
これでお仕舞い
I'm going to clash
縢が行方不明だ
'Cause I feel
二係でも執行官が一人　どさくさに紛れて逃亡を
I can always show my everything to you
監視官…
縢が逃げるかね
If this moment was for me
I try to hear, lend my ear
Voices inside
One link to join it all again
'Cause I feel
I can always show my everything to you
If this moment was for me
I try to hear, lend my ear
Voices inside
One link to join it all
So it goes again
本字幕由诸神字幕组制作 更多字幕欢迎访问http://www.kamigami.org
翻译:死树懒  白心上人   校对:西西   时间轴:葛蔓   压制：娜夏
#17: Iron Heart
Can we really say that we won?
私たち…勝ったと言えるんでしょうか？
Detective work is, by nature, about treating wounds.
デカの仕事は基本的に対症療法だ
Our investigations start after there are victims.
被害者が出てから捜査が始まる
In that sense, we lost before we even started.
そういう意味じゃはなから負けている
But at least we were able to end this lost game in a draw.
だが負け試合をせめて引き分けで終わらせることはできた
We'll just have to settle for that.
それだけで良しとするしかない
What was all that talk about the safety of the Sibyl System?
結局　シビュラシステムの安全神話って何だったんでしょうか…
Our safe and perfect society is really just an illusion.
安全完璧な社会なんてただの幻想だ
俺たちが暮らしているのは今でも危険社会なんだ
Right now, we still live in a dangerous world.
Dangerous?
危険
In this society, people depend on things that are convenient but also dangerous.
便利だが危険なものに頼った社会のことさ
Our government made us take risks.
俺たちは政府によってリスクを背負わされていた
But the risks were dispersed and distributed so cleverly that no one was able to notice.
しかしそれが巧妙に分散され分配されていたので
誰も気付けなかった
Or rather, they did notice, but they pretended that they didn't.
いや…気付いても気付かなかったことにした
Everyone might have been looking the other way.
誰もが目をそらしていたのかもしれない
I'd say that it's precisely because these things were so dangerous
危険がそこに確かに存在するが故に
that they had to act as if nothing
was wrong in order to keep their sanity.
逆に存在しないものとして扱わないと正気が保てなかった
Do you think all the citizens of this
town, myself included, were that resourceful?
この街の市民はそこまで器用だったでしょうか
私も含めて…
I don't like to lump people together
when I speak, since everyone is different,
俺は多種多様な人間を一括りにしたような話し方はあんまり好きじゃないんだが
but I'll generalize broadly here.
ここはあえて大雑把に行こう
I think humans in general are resourceful creatures.
人間は器用なものだと思う
自分の責任を回避する努力を　無意識に行うことができる
We can involuntarily try to avoid our responsibilities.
余計な話だったな
I guess I'm rambling.
Maybe I'm nervous too.
俺も浮足立っているのかもしれない
The problem is what happens next.
How they're going to judge Makishima.
槙島聖護をどう裁くか
問題はこれからだ
It's far more difficult and troublesome
a task than just shooting a Dominator.
こいつはドミネーターをぶっ放すより 遥かに難しくて厄介な仕事だ
But we can't let him get away.
だが　逃がすわけにはいかない
It's an undeniable fact that he committed crimes.
やつが罪を犯したことは厳然たる事実だ
Not to mention that we still have that idiot Kagari to worry about.
しかし残った心配は　縢のバカヤローのことだ
He went down to the basement on his own.
俺たちと別れて　地下へ向かって
Why did we lose communication with him there?
なぜそこで連絡が途絶えた
It's one day after the nightmarish riots.
This is like dealing with the aftermath of a pandemic.
まるでパンデミックの後始末だな
A Psycho-Hazard is a mental disease.
サイコハザードは精神の疾病だ
This is what happens when it's allowed to spread.
拡散すればこの有り様だ
A large number of people needing mental care,
大規模なメンタルケア　パンクした収容施設
housing facilities overflowing with people,
and economic losses due to crippled city functions.
都市機能の麻痺による経済的損失…
Makishima was a monstrous man.
槙島というのはとんでもない男でしたね
It's too early to talk about him in the past tense.
過去形にするのはまだ早い
There's still the matter of his sentencing.
やつの量刑をどうするか
The judiciary has been abolished for a while now,
裁判制度なんてなくなって久しい今
so I imagine it'll be quite difficult to
prosecute someone based solely on evidence.
証拠だけで立件するってのはちょっと難題だろうな
We're counting on you, Inspector.
頼んだぜ　監視官
You're acting too friendly, Enforcer.
なれなれしいぞ　執行官
へいへい
Okay, okay.
I've been called in by the Chief.
局長からの呼び出しだ
The cases Makishima was involved in
槙島に関する事件の取り調べは厚生大臣が編成した特殊チームで行う
will be investigated by a special
team formed by the Minister of Welfare.
The Public Safety Bureau has no
further authority to investigate this matter.
公安局は捜査権を失った
Excuse me?
はい
This is quite a unique case.
極めて特異なケースだ
Medical staff need to be present when he is questioned,
取り調べには医療スタッフも常時同席せねばならん
情報の機密性も問題になる
and we need to keep all information strictly confidential.
槙島聖護は　過去をさかのぼって様々な事件に関与していた疑いが濃厚です
Makishima Shougo was very likely to have been involved in various crimes in the past.
In order for the facts to come to light,
the Bureau needs to be able to interrogate him!
事実関係を明らかにするためにも　公安局での尋問は必須です
Are there any unsolved cases
among those past crimes you mentioned?
その過去の事件とやらに　未解決のものがあるかね
No... But...
いいえ
しかし…
Makishima will be disposed of as a research sample.
槙島は研究用の検体として処分される
Or rather, he has been disposed of.
いや　処分された
And you have more to worry about at
Division 1 than an arrested criminal, do you not?
逮捕した人間のことよりも
君の一係は大問題を抱えているだろう
An Enforcer escaped,
執行官が一人逃亡　未だ行方不明
and he's still missing.
We still don't know if he really escaped.
まだ　逃亡と決まったわけでは…
The Sibyl System has already been restored.
シビュラシステムはすでに復旧している
Enforcer Kagari hasn't been caught by the surveillance network
縢執行官が監視の網に引っ掛からないのは
because he's taking care to steer clear of it as he moves about.
それを避けて行動しているからだ
このままじゃ　責任問題になるよ
As it stands, you'll be held responsible.
That's... Well...
それは　その…
Give me a break!
ふざけるな
I demand an acceptable explanation!
納得のいく説明をしろ
執行官が偉そうに何様のつもりだ
What makes you think you can talk to me like that?! You're an Enforcer!
そんな立場の話をしてる場合か
This is not the time to discuss our positions!
We're the ones who arrested him! It makes
no damn sense that we can't even question him!
俺たちが逮捕したのに
取り調べも許されないなんておかしいだろ
It wasn't my decision.
俺が決めたことじゃない
If you want to complain...
文句があるなら…
「文句があるなら局長に直接言え」か
"If you want to complain, talk to the Chief directly." Is that it?
I'm an Enforcer. There's no way in
hell they'd let me see the Chief, is there?!
執行官の俺が局長に会えるわけないだろ
If I dare set foot in her office, it's you who'll be in trouble, Inspector.
実際に乗り込んでいったら困るのはお前だ　監視官
What's going to happen now?
どうなるんですか？　これ
There probably isn't anything else we can do.
どうにもならないんじゃないかしら
Let's put everything we have into the search for Kagari.
とにかく　こっちは縢の捜索に全力を投入する
He could well bring about the end of
the Bureau for entirely different reasons.
あいつの行動によっては　別の意味で公安局の命取りになりかねない
It's been a while, Shougo.
久しぶりだね　聖護君
It's good to see you haven't changed a bit.
変わりないようで何よりだ
You're the Chief of the Public Safety Bureau, Ms. Kasei... was it?
公安局局長　禾生さん…だったかな
I don't think we've met before.
面識はないと思うが…
Well, my appearance has changed
quite a bit over the past three years.
まあ　この三年で僕はずいぶんと様変わりしたからね
First, I need to offer you an apology
早速だが　君に謝らねばならないことがある
regarding that book I borrowed from you a while back.
以前君に借りていた本なんだが
I ended up losing it due to unfortunate, though unavoidable, circumstances.
色々と身辺がごたついたせいで　紛失してしまってね
Hm?
It was quite difficult to find another copy of that book.
同じものを探すのに苦労したよ
I'm surprised.
驚いたな…
Are you...
君は　藤間幸三郎なのか
Touma Kouzaburou?
This brings back memories.
懐かしいな あれからもう三年になるか
It's been three years, hasn't it?
When I heard that you were taken in by
the Bureau, I felt that it was terribly unfortunate.
僕は　君が公安の手に落ちたと聞いて
心底残念に思ったものだ
But that face... Plastic surgery?
しかし　その顔は整形…
No, that's not it.
いや　違うな
Considering that body structure, you're a different person.
体格からして別人だ
Your friend Senguji Toyohisa
achieved full-body cyberization too, right?
全身のサイボーグ化は　お友達の泉宮寺豊久も実現していたよね
だがここまで完璧な義体化技術は民間には公開されていない
But near-flawless artificial body
technology like this isn't available to the public.
生身の人間とまったく見分けがつかないだろ
You can't tell the difference between
this body and a human body at all, can you?
Nothing of the Touma Kouzaburou
you know is left except for his brain.
君の知っている藤間幸三郎は脳だけしか残っていない
What's going on?
どういうことなんだ
The culprit behind the grotesque
serial killings that shook society to its core
あれだけ世間を騒がせた連続猟奇殺人犯が公安局のトップだと
is now the head of the Public Safety Bureau?
冗談にも程がある
That's beyond a joke.
Technically, that's not quite true.
厳密には違う
I'm not the only Kasei Joshu,
禾生壌宗は僕一人ではないし
僕もまた常に禾生壌宗というわけではない
and I'm not always Kasei Joshu either.
Our brains are unitized, so they can be swapped easily.
僕らの脳は簡単に交換できるよう　ユニット化されていてね
We generally take turns using this body.
いつも持ち回りでこの体を使っているんだ
It also serves as a bit of a break from our everyday work.
まあ 日頃の業務の息抜きも兼ねてね
"We", you said?
「僕ら」だと
Yeah. I'm simply a representative.
ああ　僕はあくまで代表だ
I was just tasked with talking to
you here since you and I are old friends.
君と旧知の間柄　ということでこの場を任されたにすぎない
We've never shown ourselves to people,
姿を人目にさらしたことはないけれど
but I'd say we're pretty well-known by name.
僕たち名前だけならそれなりに有名だよ
I'm sure you've heard of us too.
君だって知ってるはずだ
People call us...
世間では僕らのことを「シビュラシステム」と呼んでいる
the Sibyl System!
How in the hell could they say
that Kagari just disappeared from here?!
ここから縢がどう消えるっていうんだ
No matter how worked up he got, he wouldn't run off.
あいつはどんなにテンパっても逃げたりはしない
どんなときでも自分が生き残る計算ができる男だ
He can calculate how to survive in any situation.
消えたのはあいつ自身の意思じゃない
There's no way he'd disappear of his own free will.
Then, he was abducted? Kidnapped?
だったら　拉致　誘拐…
Or he was killed in a way that
wouldn't leave any traces of his body behind.
それとも死体も残らないような殺し方か…
例えばドミネーターのデコンポーザーとかな
For example, with the Decomposer
mode of the Dominator or something.
はい　常守です
Hello. Tsunemori speaking.
We've received a report from a citizen.
市民からの通報があった
They've found an abandoned, broken Dominator.
故障したドミネーターが放棄されていたそうだ
There's at least twenty kilometers
between the Nona Tower and this location.
ノナタワーからここまで２０ｋｍはある
Even among all the chaos caused by the riots,
いくら暴動の混乱後とはいえ
is it really possible that he wasn't caught even once by the cameras?
１回もカメラチェックに引っ掛からないなんてことがあるのか
There's no mistake that this is Kagari's Dominator.
ドミネーターは間違いなく縢のものです
It's damaged quite a bit.
かなりひどく損傷してます
The built-in GPS isn't functioning either.
内蔵ＧＰＳも機能していない
Did he break it himself?
自分で壊した 追跡を逃れるために
To avoid being tracked?
Or is this all a ploy by someone who wants us to think exactly that?
あるいはそう思わせたい誰かの偽装工作…
This time, just like every other,
今回の事件
目の付けどころはさすがというほかない
you managed to aim straight for the right target.
実際君のお仲間は真実にたどりついていたよ
In fact, your friend managed to discover the truth.
What the hell is this?!
「何なんだ？こりゃ…」
This is... the true form of the Sibyl System!
「こいつがシビュラシステムの正体だ」
The Sibyl System is said to use a PDP model—
シビュラシステムはいわゆるＰＤＰモデル
an extensive network of supercomputers
performing parallel distributed processing.
大量のスーパーコンピューターによる並列分散処理ということになっている
It's not really a lie, but it's far from the truth.
嘘ではないが それは実態とは程遠い
Its ability to draw inferences based on a vast knowledge base
was not achieved solely by speed gains in conventional computing.
ナレッジベースの活用と推論機能の実現は
ただ従来の演算の高速化によって実現したわけではない
Parallelizing the system that was able to do those things and expanding it mechanically
それが可能だったシステムを並列化し
機械的に拡張することで
simply gave it massive processing ability compared to before.
膨大な処理能力を与えただけのことだったのさ
In fact, a system that expands and speeds up its
ability to think by incorporating human brain activity
人体の脳の活動を統合し
思考力を拡張 高速化するシステムは
was already put into practical use more than fifty years ago.
実はもう５０年以上も前から実用化されていた
It's precisely because we kept this
technology secret and used it carefully
この技術を秘匿し 慎重に運用したからこそ
that today our country is able to function as the only nation on Earth ruled by law.
わが国は目下のところ地球上で唯一の法治国家として機能できている
We don't even have to destroy this.
「この手でぶち壊すまでもねえ」
If we make this public, it'll be the end of this country.
「こいつを世間に公表すればこの国はおしまいだ」
And this time—
The system currently has 247 constituent members.
目下システムの構成員は２４７名
By having about 200 of the 247
connected in sessions at any given time,
うち２００名ほどが順番にセッションを組むことで
we can continuously monitor and judge the
Psycho-Pass of every single person in this country.
この国の全人口のサイコパスを常時監視し
判定し続けることが可能だ
Mechanical programs alone can determine,
at most, stress measurements based on the Hue Check.
結局のところ　機械的なプログラムで判定できるのは
せいぜいが色相診断によるストレス計測までだ
Determining Crime Coefficients, which indicate a more profound assessment of human nature,
より深遠な人間の本質を示す犯罪係数の特定には
requires a higher degree of thinking ability and judgment.
もっと高度な思考力と判断力が要求される
And we are the ones who can make it happen.
それを実現し得るのが われわれなんだよ
What a joke.
お笑いぐさだな
They said we lived in a fair society managed by machines.
人間のエゴに依存しない 機械による公平な社会の運営
One that didn't depend on flawed human egos.
That's how they presented the Sibyl
System, and that's why people accepted it.
そううたわれていたからこそ
民衆はシビュラシステムを受け入れてきたというのに…
And yet, all those judgments were made
arbitrarily by you, an aggregate of human brains?
その実体が人間の脳の集合体である
君たちによる恣意的なものだったのか
No. The system is boundlessly fair.
いいや　限りなく公平だとも
We judge and supervise people as those who transcend mankind.
民衆を審判し監督しているわれわれは
すでに人類を超越した存在だ
The first qualification to be a constituent member of the Sibyl System
シビュラシステムの構成員たる第一の資格は
is to have an irregular personality that
doesn't fit in with mankind's conventional standards.
従来の人類の規範に収まらないイレギュラーな人格の持ち主であることだ
Instead of aimlessly empathizing with others,
いたずらに他者に共感することも 情に流されることもなく
instead of losing yourself to emotion,
you should be able to oversee
human actions from an outsider's viewpoint.
人間の行動を外側の観点から俯瞰し裁定できる
That talent is what we require.
そういう才能が望まれる
For example, yourself and I.
例えば　この僕や君がそうであるように
Oh?
ほう…
I'm also a unique human. One whose Crime
Coefficient can't be determined from their Psycho-Pass.
僕もね　サイコパスから犯罪係数が特定できない特殊な人間だ
It's caused me a great deal of loneliness over the years.
おかげでずいぶんと孤独な思いをしたものだ
A personality that cannot be
measured, even by Sibyl's collective intellect,
そのようなシビュラの総意をしても計り知れないパーソナリティーは
is called "criminally asymptomatic".
「免罪体質」と呼ばれている
Those with this personality are distinguished from all other citizens
凡百の市民とは一線を画す新たな思想と価値観の持ち主
by their unique ideology and sense of values.
By finding such valuable people and taking them in,
そういう貴重な人材を見つけて取り込むことで
the system has continued to expand its range of thinking
システムは常に思考の幅を拡張し
and gained new possibilities as an intellectual form.
知性体として新たな可能性を獲得してきた
I see. So that's why you disappeared instead
of being executed after the Bureau took you in.
そうか…
公安局の手に落ちた君が処刑されることもなく姿を消したのは…
Yes. I was welcomed as a member of the Sibyl System.
ああ　こうしてシビュラシステムの一員に加えられたのさ
At first, I was confused, but it didn't take long
before I was able to understand its true splendor.
初めは戸惑ったがね
すぐにその素晴らしさが理解できた
Omnipotence, achieved through expanding both understanding and judgment by sharing one's cognition with other brains...
他者の脳と認識を共有し
理解力と判断力を拡張されることの全能感
I feel like I'm a prophet straight out of legend.
神話に登場する預言者の気分だよ
I understand everything.
何もかもが分かる
I feel that everything in the world is under my rule.
世界の全てを自分の支配下に感じる
人一人の肉体が獲得し得る快楽には限度がある
There are limits to the amount of
pleasure a person can obtain in the flesh.
However, pleasure brought out by the intellect is infinite.
だが知性がもたらす快楽は無限だ
聖護君 君なら理解できるんじゃないか
You can understand that, can't you, Shougo?
Yeah. It's not really hard to imagine.
そうだな…想像に難くないところではある
僕も君もこの矛盾に満ちた世界で孤立し 迫害されてきた
Both you and I have been isolated and
oppressed in this world full of contradictions.
But we don't need to grieve over it anymore.
だがもうそれを嘆く必要はない
We should be proud of the nobility of
this mission that fate has charged us with.
僕たちは共に運命として課された
使命の崇高さを誇るべきなんだ
君もまた しかるべき地位を手に入れるときが来たんだ
The time has also come for you to take your proper place!
つまり…
In other words...
you're telling me to become a member of the Sibyl System?
僕もまたシビュラシステムの一員になれ…と
Your intellect and deep insight
君の知性 深遠なる洞察力
are qualities we eagerly seek out in
order to further evolve the Sibyl System.
それはシビュラシステムのさらなる進化のために
われわれが求めてやまないものだ
It's not to say that we can't simply make you a member by force.
強引な手段で君をシステムの一員に取り込むことはできなくはないが…
However, "Value exists only in the acts based on one's free will".
「意思に基づいた行動のみが価値を持つ」
というのは君の言葉だったよね
Those were your words, right?
I hoped that you'd understand my explanation and then agree to it.
君ならば僕の説明を理解した上で同意してくれると判断したんだ
機械の部品に成り果てろというのもぞっとしない話だな
The idea of being reduced to a cog
in a machine isn't very appealing to me.
Of course, this would not take away
any of your independence as an individual.
もちろん　これは君の固体としての自立性を損なうような要求ではない
In fact, as you can see, I'm still maintaining a sense of my self as Touma Kouzaburou.
現に僕はこうして今も藤間幸三郎としての自我を保っている
All you have to do is say a single word: "Yes."
君はただ一言「ＹＥＳ」とうなずいてくれるだけでいい
The operation will be completed on our way to the
Ministry of Welfare using the equipment we have here.
ここにある設備だけで厚生省に向かう道すがら
外科的な処置は完了する
The Makishima Shougo known to
the public will disappear with your body,
槙島聖護という公の存在は肉体と共に消失するが
君は誰に知られることもなくこの世界を統べる支配者の一員となる
but you'll become one of those who
rule this world and none will be the wiser.
You sound like the doctor in Balnibarbi.
まるでバルニバービの医者だな
何だって
What?
I'm talking about "Gulliver's Travels" by Swift. Specifically, Part III.
スウィフトの『ガリヴァー旅行記』だよ
その第三編
ガリヴァーが空飛ぶ島ラピュータの後に訪問するのがバルニバービだ
Balnibarbi is the place Gulliver
travels to after the flying island of Laputa.
A doctor in Balnibarbi comes up with a way to get
politicians with conflicting opinions to reconcile with one another.
バルニバービのある医者が対立した政治家を融和させる方法を思い付く
２人の脳を半分に切断して
It was surgery in which they'd cut each of their brains in half then have the two hemispheres sewn together.
再びつなぎ合わせるという手術だ
Once that was done, they could "produce
the moderation as well as regularity of thinking".
これが成功すると
節度のある調和の取れた思考が可能になるという
For the self-conceited lot
この世界を監視し 支配するために生まれてきたとうぬぼれている連中には
who think that "they come into the
world only to watch and govern its motion",
何よりも望ましい方法だと
Swift writes that it is the most desirable approach.
スウィフトは書いている
You're a genius at sarcasm, Shougo.
聖護君は皮肉の天才だな
I'm not, but Swift certainly is.
僕ではなくスウィフトがね
You probably thought that I wouldn't resist until I knew where I was,
場所が分からないうちは抵抗しないと考えたんだろうが
相変わらず君は詰めが甘い
but as usual, you weren't very careful.
You said "on our way to the Ministry of Welfare" earlier.
さっきの「厚生省に向かう道すがら」という言葉
By saying that, you hinted that we're in transit.
あれで移動中だとほのめかしてしまった
We're not inside the Public Safety
Bureau, so I judged that I could escape.
ここは公安局の中ではない
だから逃げられると僕は判断した
Why?
なぜだ
I thought you'd be able to understand...
君なら理解できたはずだ
この全能の愉悦を…世界を統べる快感を…
the joy of omnipotence and the pleasure of governing the world...
Like God, you mean?
さながら神のごとくかね
That might be pleasurable in its own way,
それはそれで良い気分になれるのかもしれないが
あいにく審判やレフェリーは趣味じゃないんだ
but unfortunately I'm not into being an umpire or a referee.
I can't genuinely enjoy the game unless I'm part of it.
そんな立場では 試合を純粋に楽しめないからね
And I love this game that people
call "life" from the bottom of my heart.
僕はね この人生というゲームを心底愛しているんだよ
That's why I'd like to continue to
participate in it as a player, forever and ever.
だからどこまでも プレーヤーとして参加し続けたい
S-Stop it!
や…やめろ…
What's that? Are you afraid of dying,
even after attaining the omniscience of God?
神の意識を手に入れても死ぬのは怖いかい
There's no way I could love anyone,
Dareka wo aisuru koto nante
Dekiru wake nakutte
But I wish to be loved by someone in turn
The world may not have
Dakedo dareka ni aisaretakute
Ended yesterday after all,
Kawaranai kinou ga zutto tsuzuita to shite mo
But we will not budge
Doko ni mo ike ya shinainda
watashi to kimi
From where we are
Kamisama doko he itte shimatta no nee
God, in favor of which parts have you left us?
Henji wa nakute itsu datte sou da yo
I receive no reply, I never do
Are you still here?
You'll never walk alone
I walk with you
Anata to iku
Donna tsumi mo
I will share all your sins
Seotte ageru
Together with you
Michi naki michi wo
Aruiteku no
I walk
A trackless path
Anata to futari de
Sorry for calling so late.
夜分失礼する
Am I correct in assuming that
this is Kougami Shinya's number?
狡噛慎也の番号で間違いなかったかな
Today, I came to know the true form of the Sibyl System.
今日 シビュラシステムの正体を知ったよ
It's not something worth putting your life on the line to protect.
あれは君が命懸けで守るほど価値のあるものではない
それだけを伝えておきたくてね
I just wanted to let you know that.
Well then, I'll see you around.
では　いずれまた…
Hey, Gino! What the hell happened?!
おいギノ いったい何があった
Where did you hear about it?
お前…どこでそれを…
So what happened?!
どうなんだ
まだ確認は取れていないが
It hasn't been confirmed,
槙島を乗せた輸送機が…
but the transport aircraft Makishima was on
seems to have crashed.
墜落したらしい…
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".